Look with your heart and truly see
Find that the truth is not far away
Hey you good or bad, truth or lies
Can't escape this gray smoke of the heart
Bring along all of your courage
And maybe you can save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
The computer game MagiEye Angel is all the rage in Tuna Town
Even Jingjing is hooked on it
Meanwhile, many players are falling ill one after another
This seems to be inextricably linked to the Illumin-Eye
Heart of Vitality
Locky, how's Jingjing doing now?
The doctor says her symptoms match those mysterious coma patients we were investigating
They can't find the cause
How strange. Even Jingjing couldn't resist
There's definitely something fishy about this game
What's going on?
Quick, check on Jingjing!
Strange. Where did the doctors and nurses go?
Locky, don't go over there! It's too dangerous!
Damn it!
They're all under MagiEye's control now
So what do we do now?
Take Jingjing and get out of here!
Try not to look at those screens.
The Illumin-Eye has appeared on every screen!
Don't look!
If you do, you'll never come back.
What are all these lights?
Uncle! Uncle! Wake up!
Please wake up, Uncle!
Wh-what's going on?
We're in big trouble this time.
Th-this place...
Seems we've landed somewhere incredible.
And Jingjing is gone too.
Now what do we do?
H-Hawxing?
Hawxing, you're in the game too?
I infiltrated the game to investigate.
You weaklings, get out of here while you can.
Even though you saved me,
I still hate you.
The situation is critical.
This evil game
has taken control of everyone.
We have to save them all.
We need to find a way to catch the one behind this game.
There are abnormal energy signals flowing in virtual space.
What's this?
Following this energy will definitely lead us to a clue.
Where did you get that tool?
It's just mental manifestation.
The game world can turn everything people imagine
into physical form.
Do we have to use this tool
to ride on the energy flow?
According to my calculations,
going along the energy flow
can get us to the energy source endpoint in the shortest time.
And this single-board tool
can reduce drag to a minimum.
But be careful.
A high-intensity energy flow
is enough to destroy a building.
In the game world, people can
fulfill desires that can't be fulfilled in the real world.
That's why these games are so popular.
Uncle! I almost touched the energy flow!
Don't shake.
Help!
Wait, Uncle!
I thought I heard Jingjing's voice.
What?
That... that's...
Locky!
Was that really Jingjing just now?
That's Jingjing.
Jingjing, are you okay?
Locky, you came.
Don't worry, Jingjing.
We're definitely going to get you out of here.
It was The Illumin-Eye that trapped me here.
The Illumin-Eye, them again. Damn them.
The Illumin-Eye has collected so much energy.
There must be a major purpose.
We need to find out.
Found it.
What's up?
Hawxing?
Did you find something?
This... what is this?
MagiEye's energy convergence point.
Just destroy this.
Welcome to the charming Heart of Vitality.
Who?
That's a very good question.
Don't be afraid, my dear friend.
It's you again, you annoying pest.
What exactly are you trying to do?
There's no harm in telling you.
Vitality and youth are wasted on the likes of you.
You might as well hand them over to us, The Illumin-Eye, for safekeeping.
You money-grubbing game makers.
I won't let you get away with this.
Guards!
Take good care of our honored guests.
Heart of Vitality collection complete.
Thanks to all our dear players for your kind support.
We can't let him get away with this.
Stop him!
Mission accomplished.
Dazzling vitality and energy
As adorable as an Oscar statuette.
Dear little friends,
See you on our next show!
What's going on?
What happened?
I've got no strength left.
Doctor!
Quick, call a doctor!
So pretty
Yeah
We really should get out more often
Now that game was a real thrill
But it was so scary
Jingjing's never playing that again
The Illumin-Eye took the Heart of Vitality
Their plan succeeded this time
Who knows what schemes they'll come up with next
[MagiEye Angel]
[Ending Song]
Bright eyes are twinkling
Smiles facing the sunshine
Bravely speak that little touch of feeling treasured in your heart
Music brings the morning breeze
Taking away the wish of many years
It will quietly be planted at the crossroads of Qian'an Station